Guide to the Lucien L. Nunn papers [ca.1863-1971]
Nunn, Lucien L. papers [ca.1863-1971]
- Series VI. Photographs
  - Technical Photographs
    - 36 - Ontario - Ontario Power Plant, area photography and station interiors - 1905, 1908, 7 envelopes (Box 45)
    - 37 - Logan Canyon, Utah - grounds and interiors - 1905, ca. 1910, 3 envelopes (Box 45)
    - 38 - Olmsted - turbine, tunnel, lower thrust block, east pipe, flume - ca. 1904-1908 (Box 47)
    - 38 - Olmsted - turbine, tunnel, lower thrust block, east pipe, flume - ca. 1904-1908 (Box 53)
    - 39 - Bear Lake - Montpelier, Idaho - landscapes, structures, and projects at Bear Lake and Bear River - ca. 1903-1913, 8 envelopes
    - 40 - Niagara Falls - Ontario Power Company - construction - 1905, 5 envelopes (Box 53)
    - 41 - Olmsted, Ithaca/Cornell, Grace, Boise, etc. - Paul P. Ashworth's photo album - ca. 1911-1916, 1937, 1954 (Box 52)
    - 42 - Olmsted - Olmsted under construction - ca. 1903-1904 (Box 48)
    - 43 - Nunn's Station - equipment - n.d. (Box 53)
    - 44 - Nunn's Station - man with equipment - n.d. (Box 53)
    - 45 - unidentified location - enlargements of photos of electrical equipment - n.d. (Box 49)
    - 46 - Colorado - the electrical distributing lines and waterways of the Telluride Power Company in Colorado - n.d. (Box 49)
    - 47 - various locations - photographs previously to be used in a book on electrical power - annotated, explanations enclosed - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 49)
    - 48 - Mercur, Utah - Book of Photographs, "Electrical Installation--Golden Gate Mill" - n.d. (Box 55)
    - 49 - Niagara - technical drawings - Ontario Power Company - 1904-1905, 6 envelopes (Box 56)
    - 50 - unidentified electrical site - mounted photos - 1902, 2 envelopes (Box 56)
    - 51 - Illium, Colorado - Illium flume with drafted cross section - 1907, 2 envelopes (Box 56)
    - 52 - Mercur, Utah - Mine & Mill - n.d., 9 envelopes (Box 47, 57)
    - 53 - unidentified sites - "L.L. Nunn Special" - sites, landscapes, equipment, 6 envelopes (Box 47)
    - 54 - Olmsted - electrical equipment - 1907-1909, 2 envelopes (Box 58)
    - 55 - unidentified location(s)- numbered technical photos - n.d. (Box 58)
    - 56 - Olmsted - 40 K.V. cutout - 1908
    - 57 - Olmsted - structures, landscapes, and equipment - ca. 1905-1909, 14 envelopes (Box 57)
    - 58 - Telluride area - Grace, Nunn's Station, Olmsted, etc. - glass negatives - ca. 1900s-1910s, 1907, 10 envelopes (Box 47, 57)
    - 59 - Idaho? - book of photos - "Current Electrical Development," etc. - n.d. (Box 58)
    - 60 - Nunn's Station - equipment - 1901 (Box 58)
    - 61 - Nunn's Station - enlargement of photo of train - n.d. (Box 40)
    - 62 - Grace - pipe and generators - 1910 (Box 47)
    - 63 - Olmsted - blueprints for Olmsted power house - n.d. (Box 53)
    - 64 - Olmsted - switchboard - annotated - 1906 (Box 53)
    - 65 - Provo - failure of experimental 40,000 volt towers - 1907 (Box 53)
    - 66 - Telluride - motor at Telluride mine - ca. 1905 (Box 47)
    - 67 - Olmsted - changes in penstocks for installation of Francis turbines - 1908 (Box 53)
    - 68 - Nunn's Station? - unidentified train - n.d. (Box 53)
    - 69 - Bliss, Idaho - pictures sent by L.B. Fuller to L.L. Nunn showing slicks works and flume - 1911 (Box 47)
    - 70 - Niagara - Niagara Power Station - annotated - ca. 1905 (Box 40)
    - 71 - Lower Salmon Plant of the Great Shoshone and Twin Falls Water Power Company - ca. 1914 (Box 53)
    - 72 - unidentified location - electricity experiment? - possible exhibit material - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 57)
    - 73 - unidentified location - 60,000 volt lightning arrester test - 1906 (Box 53)
    - 74 - Illium - construction of Illium flume - annotated - 1905 (Box 53)
    - 75 - unidentified location - numbered photos of standard and wrecked towers - n.d. (Box 47)
    - 76 - Casper Station - construction of Casper Station - from L.L. Nunn's desk - n.d. (Box 47)
    - 77 - various locations - photo enlargements of early power installations, environs, etc. - n.d., 8 envelopes (Box 59)
  - Nunn Personal
    - 1 - Nunn's photo albums - n.d., 7 envelopes; 1 book (Box 40, 51, 61)
    - 2 - studio and candid photographs of Nunn - ca. 1891-1918, 26 envelopes (Box 40, 51)
    - 3 - Nunn family photographs - ca. 1880's-1910's, 30 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 4 - identified photographs of friends, colleagues, etc. - ca. 1880's-1910's, 19 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 5 - unidentified photographs of friends, colleagues, etc. - ca. 1880's-1910's, 24 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 6 - Olmsted - Nunn's photographs of Olmsted, "Slick's Resort," etc. - n.d., 7 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 7 - unidentified area photographs - n.d., 4 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 8 - Deep Springs - Nunn on port of Main Building, Nunn and O.B. Suhr - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 51)
    - 9 - Deep Springs - group portrait with L.L. and P.N. Nunn - 1919 (Box 51)
    - 10 - Provo, Utah - L.L. Nunn's house - 1905 (Box 51)
- Series VII. Miscellany
  - Republican Campaign Book, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Republican Campaign Book & Articles, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Harvard Business School Alumni Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - The National Geographic Magazine, January 1918 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Address to Lincoln University by F.J. Rarig, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Time Table - Denver & Rio Grande Railroad (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Blotter Advertising for Aetna Insurance Co. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Financial and Mining Record, Jan. 2 & March 25, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 5-inch Magnetic Tape, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - A.M. Wrench papers found at Deep Springs, Summer 1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 5 Books that belonged to Charles D. Walcott - Proceedings of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1876 - 1880 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence & Documents, 1900-1901, 1937-1939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Badges (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "George Lincoln Burr" (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Loyalty and Liberty" by George Lincoln Burr (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "The Freedom of History" by George Lincoln Burr, January 1917 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Telluride and San Miguel County, Colorado" (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Graphic Library: History of the U.S. Tariff" Aug. 1888 & "Life and History of Grover Cleveland" July 1888 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Department of the Interior - United States Geological Survey, "Manual of Topographic Methods" by Henry Gannet, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report - "Our Twentieth Year" by the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington, July 1, 1958-June 30, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Souvenir of the Congressional Party's trip to Hawaii, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "The Diaries of Andrew D. White" ed. by Robert Morris Ogden (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Obituary Notice - Sidgwick, Nevil Vincent (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "The Satellite Tracking Camera" by Joseph Nunn of Joseph Nunn & Associates (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bank Statements of G.G. Tucker (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bills to G.G. Tucker from various merchants (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Check to Mr. L. Crowell for $10 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings - Early Telluride, Colorado (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Guide & Map - 4-Corners County, Colorado (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Map of Lot for Sale by Davis & Stringer (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Manual - First Congregational Church, Telluride, Colorado, 1889 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Photograph of man shoveling snow (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - The Telluride Times, December 26, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Republican Publishing Co. Receipts (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Documents re: Western Federation of Miners Strike, Strikebreakers & Letter from one Mining Superintendent to another, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Idarado Mining Company Map (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Homestake Mining Company, Colorado, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Reports- Wood's Hole Marine Biological Laboratory, 1892-1895 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Report - Wood's Hole Marine Biological Laboratory, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Documents re: Heating of Telluride Club House, September 22-23, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Pamphlets & Booklets I (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Pamphlets & Booklets II (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Prospectives/Journals from various schools I (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Prospectives/Journals from various schools II (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Prospectives/Journals from various schools III (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Book Catalogs I, 1889-1913 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Book Catalogs II, 1889-1913 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Offprints of Congressional Speeches on the Tariff (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter I (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter II (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter III (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter IV (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter V (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter VI (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter VII (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Legal & Congressional Matter VIII (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Amsted Branch cash book (volume 12), 1910-1912 (Box 64)
  - Amsted Branch ledger (volume 13), 1911 (Box 64)
  - Telluride Institute cash book, (volume 25), 1908-1911 (Volume 25)
  - Audio reels (Box 71)
    18 mostly unlabeled reels of audio recordings. One appears to say Waldo, one is labeled O J Sweeting recorded by Helen Heckman, one says F. c. Noon, DS June 8
  - Audio reels (Box 71)
- Series VIII. Orville Sweeting
  - General
    - Captions (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Captions (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Captions (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Davis Foundation (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Support (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Envelopes & Letter Head for End Papers (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Telluride, Colorado Friends (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Bailey, Parker (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Bailey, Parker (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - Blair, Frank (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Jones, Paul (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Walcott, Sid & Frank Noon (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Wesely, Ed (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Wight, F.J. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - Women & Telluride Association (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Research Material
    - RM Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - RM Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - RM Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - RM Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - RM Correspondence - Burr, George Lincoln (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - RM Correspondence - Description of L.L. Nunn Papers (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - RM Correspondence - Nunn (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - RM Correspondence - Nunn (copies) (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - RM Correspondence - Utah Power & Light (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - RM Correspondence - Telluride Association (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - RM Correspondence - Telluride Association (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - RM Correspondence - Search for Water Power, Fillmore Forest Lawsuit, and Gifford Pinchot (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - RM Correspondence - Westinghouse, 1969, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - RM Correspondence - Wormuth (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Research Material (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Research Material (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Research Material (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Research Material (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Research Material (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Research Material (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Research Material (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Research Material (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Research Material (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Butler, Gen. Benjamin (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Burr, George Lincoln (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Clippings - Colorado, 1889-1892 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Clippings & Transcripts of Notes from G.L. Burr's Address, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Branch of T.A. to 1920 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Deep Spring's - History (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Deep Springs (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Misc. items, Utah, Telluride Association and Power Co., Does not appear to contain Federal Heights SLC, etc, but was labeled as such. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lavender, David (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Maps (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Notes (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Notes (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Nunn Enterprises - Employees (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Oral History Transcripts (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Oral History Transcripts - Wood's Hole 1897 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Power - Historical Articles (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Reminiscences (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Smithsonian Rept. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Telluride & San Miguel Co. I (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Telluride & San Miguel Co. II (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Telluride Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Telluride Tax Exemption (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Utah Power & Light (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Westinghouse - Bio (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Westinghouse & Edison Articles, 1889 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Work Requirement (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Wrench, A.M. - Scrapbook of Telluride, CO (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Photos - Individuals, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Photos (copies) I (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Photos (copies) II (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Photos (copies) III (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sweeting Photo Project
    - SPP (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - SPP (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Ames & Illium (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Ames & Illium (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Ames & Illium (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Olmstead (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Olmstead (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Undated Manuscript 1, Edited (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Table of Contents, Foreward (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 1, Early Mining Ventures (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 2, Early Years of L.L. Nunn (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 3, L.L. Nunn Pioneer (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 4, L.L. Nunn, Electrical Engineer (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 5, The World's First Alternating Current Power Plant is Constructed (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 6, Early Telluride Power Developments in Colorado (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 7, Office of L.L. Nunn (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 8, The San Miguel Consolidated Gold Mining Co. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 9, Construction of the First Great Power Plant in the Niagara Gorge (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 10, Utah Developments in Provo Canyon (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 11, Development of Bear Lake (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 12, The Telluride Institution Idea (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 13, Premonitions of Disaster (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 14, Recruitment of Telluride Institute Pinheads (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 15, The Student Body (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 16, James Campbell Attempts to Seize the Power Company (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 17, Founding of Telluride Association (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 18, The Search for Water Powers (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 19, Beaver River Power Company (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 20, Telluride Association, The Initial Years 1910-1918 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 20, Continued (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 20, Continued - The Founding of Deep Springs (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 20 (copy) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 21, Telluride Association and Deep Springs 1920-1925 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 22, The Man Required for Deep Springs (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 22, Continued (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 23, Nunn Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 23, Continued (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Chapter 23, Continued (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Undated Manuscript 2 - Omitted Chapter (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Title Page, Contents, Preface & Chapter 1 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 2, L.L. Nunn (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 3, Nunn's Removal to CO in 1880 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 4, First Intentions to Electrify the San Juan Mines Near Telluride (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 5, Office of L.L. Nunn (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter [5 or 6], The San Miguel Consolidated Mining Co. (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 6, Ames Provo Station, Operating in 1891 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 7, L.L. Nunn's Early Educational Work (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 8, Expansion of Telluride Power Company in Utah (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 9, Beaver River Power Company (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 10, Power Development at Niagara Falls (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 11, Founding of the Telluride Institute at Olmstead & The Campbell Takeover Attempt (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter [12 or 13], Telluride Power Co. Sale to Utah Power & Light Co. (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter [13 or 14], George Lincoln Burr, Second Founder of Telluride Association (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - January 1975 Manuscript - Chapter [14 or 15], Founding of a Primary Educational Branch, Deep Springs, CA (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Title Page, Contents, Preface, Chapter 1 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 2, L.L. Nunn's Investigation of Altering-Current Electricity (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 3, The Ames Power Plant, Built & Operated Successfully (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 4, Founding of the Telluride Power Company In Colorado (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 5, Extension of Telluride Power into Utah (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 6, Nunn's Role in the Development of Niagara Fall Power (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 7, L.L. Nunn as Educator (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 8, A Model for Service (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 9, The Telluride Educational Work is Perpetuated (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - July 1975 Manuscript - Chapter 10, The Founding of Deep Springs (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 1, Early Mining Ventures in the San Juan Mountains (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 2, L.L. Nunn's Investigation of Alternating-Current Electricity (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 3, The Ames Power Plant, Built & Operated Successfully (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 4, Founding of the Telluride Power Company in Colorado (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 5, Extension of Telluride Into Utah (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 6, Nunn's Role in the Development of Niagara Falls Power (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 7, L.L. Nunn as Educator (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 8, Can Business & Education Mix? (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 9, The Telluride Educational Work is Perpetuated (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - March 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 10, The Founding of Deep Springs (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Title Page & Contents (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 1, pages 1-6, Early Mining Ventures in San Juan County (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 2, pages 7-30, Investigation of Alternating-Current Electricity (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 3, pages 31-72, The Ames Power Plant (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 4, pages 73-102, Fouding of Telluride Power Company in Colorado (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 5, pages 103-147, Extension of Telluride Power Into Utah (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 6, pages 148-157, Nunn's Role in the Development of Niagara Falls Power (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 7, pages 158-198, L.L. Nunn as Educator (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 8, pages 199-233, Can Business & Education Mix? (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 9, pages 234-280, Telluride Educational Work is Perpetuated (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - April 1976 Manuscript - Chapter 10, pages 281-322, The Founding of Deep Springs (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - "The Education Experiment of L.L. Nunn," by Orville Sweeting (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - "The Education Experiment of L.L. Nunn," by Orville Sweeting (Box 24, Folder 33)